
[
  {
    "question": "a particular way of walking ",
    "choice1": "gait",
    "choice2": "britches",
    "choice3": "muskrat",
    "choice4": "boxcars",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Pants (trousers) that do not cover the whole leg",
    "choice1": "gait",
    "choice2": "britches",
    "choice3": "muskrat",
    "choice4": "boxcars",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "a North American animal that lives in or near water",
    "choice1": "gait",
    "choice2": "britches",
    "choice3": "muskrat",
    "choice4": "boxcars",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "a section of a train that has a roof and large, sliding doors and that carries goods and supplies rather than people",
    "choice1": "gait",
    "choice2": "britches",
    "choice3": "muskrat",
    "choice4": "boxcars",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "a short, heavy thick stick that is mainly used by police officers",
    "choice1": "Billy clubs",
    "choice2": "alias",
    "choice3": "gory",
    "choice4": "accordian",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "an additional name that a person(such as a criminal) sometimes uses",
    "choice1": "Billy clubs",
    "choice2": "alias",
    "choice3": "gory",
    "choice4": "accordian",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Involving a lot of violence and blood",
    "choice1": "Billy clubs",
    "choice2": "alias",
    "choice3": "gory",
    "choice4": "accordian",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "a musical instrument that is shaped like a box andthat is held in your hands and played by pulling its sides apart and them pushing them together while pressing buttons and keys",
    "choice1": "Billy clubs",
    "choice2": "alias",
    "choice3": "gory",
    "choice4": "accordian",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "a message sent by a telegraph (wire) and delivered in written (printed) form",
    "choice1": "telegram",
    "choice2": "slew",
    "choice3": "paltry",
    "choice4": "judgmental",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "a large number of people or things",
    "choice1": "telegram",
    "choice2": "slew",
    "choice3": "paltry",
    "choice4": "judgmental",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "very small or too small an amount",
    "choice1": "telegram",
    "choice2": "slew",
    "choice3": "paltry",
    "choice4": "judgmental",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Disapproving; judging someone too quickly and critically",
    "choice1": "telegram",
    "choice2": "slew",
    "choice3": "paltry",
    "choice4": "judgmental",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "causing feelings of hatred or disgust; repulsive; very bad",
    "choice1": "loathsome",
    "choice2": "resourceful",
    "choice3": "dignity",
    "choice4": "slew",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "able to deal well with new or difficult situations and to find solutions to problems",
    "choice1": "loathsome",
    "choice2": "resourceful",
    "choice3": "dignity",
    "choice4": "paltry",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "a sense of pride in oneself; self respect",
    "choice1": "loathsome",
    "choice2": "resourceful",
    "choice3": "dignity",
    "choice4": "gait",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
  